{
  "decks": [
    {
      "name": "Check",
      "description": "This is a deck to study",
      "id": 1
    },
    {
      "name": "Test",
      "description": "Test Deck",
      "id": 2
    }
  ],
  "cards": [
    {
      "front": "What number card is this?",
      "back": "Card number 1",
      "deckId": null,
      "id": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "What number card is this one?",
      "back": "Card #2",
      "deckId": null,
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "front": "Is this the final card?",
      "back": "Yes. This is card number 3.",
      "deckId": null,
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "front": "Card 2",
      "back": "Back",
      "deckId": null,
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "front": "Card 3",
      "back": "Back",
      "deckId": null,
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "front": "Card 4",
      "back": "Back",
      "deckId": null,
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "front": "Card 1",
      "back": "Back of card 1",
      "deckId": null,
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "front": "Card 2",
      "back": "Back of Card 2",
      "deckId": null,
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "front": "Card 3",
      "back": "Back of card 3",
      "deckId": null,
      "id": 9
    },
    {
      "front": "Card 1",
      "back": "Back of Card 1",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 10
    },
    {
      "front": "Card 2",
      "back": "Back of Card 2",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 11
    },
    {
      "front": "Card 3",
      "back": "Back of Card 3",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 12
    }
  ]
}